all right welcome everyone and thank you
好的，欢迎大家，谢谢
so much for coming I'm Eric and today
非常重要，我是Eric，今天
we're going to talk a bit about g1
我们将谈谈g1
concepts and performance tuning but
概念和性能调优，但
before we begin I'm gonna let this slide
在我们开始之前，我先放这张幻灯片
hang out there for a few awkward seconds
在那里呆了几秒钟
for all of you to enjoy alright let's
让大家享受吧
have a look at today's agenda we're
看看我们今天的议程
gonna start off by looking at three
从三点开始
important properties when it comes to
重要的特性
garbage collection throughput latency
垃圾收集吞吐量延迟
and footprint we're now gonna move on to
和足迹，我们现在要继续
see how you can measure the JVM and the
了解如何衡量JVM和
garbage collector after that we're gonna
之后垃圾收集器
get into some tuning and in the end
进行一些调整，最后
we're gonna talk a little bit about the
我们将谈论一些
community but first who am i up here I'm
社区，但首先我是谁
Eric I like to program garbage
我喜欢对Eric编程垃圾
collectors I work at Oracle in the JVM
我在JVM中在Oracle工作的收集器
garbage collection team and has done so
垃圾收集小组已经这样做了
for approximately six years and for the
大约六年
past three years I've worked on the g1
过去三年来我一直在研究g1
garbage collector and I was a reviewer
垃圾收集器，我是评论员
and frequent committer to OPI decay so
和OPI衰减的频繁提交者，因此
let's go into our first point for today
让我们进入今天的第一点
throughput latency and footprint these
吞吐延迟和占用空间
three important properties can roughly
三个重要的属性可以大致
be defined us for free put the number of
被定义为我们免费放的数量
requests per second so if you have a web
每秒的请求数，如果您有网络
server or some other back-end service
服务器或其他一些后端服务
the number of requests you can handle
您可以处理的请求数
per second for latency you can think of
每秒的延迟，您可以想到
that as the maximum time for a request
作为请求的最长时间
and for footprint well that's usually
对于脚印来说，通常
consider just a memory usage of a Java
考虑一下Java的内存使用情况
process and we're gonna look about the a
流程，我们将探讨
little bit more on each of these
这些都多一点
properties in detail so for throughput
详细的属性，以便获得吞吐量
we usually measure that as the total
我们通常将其作为总数
running time of the Java process and
Java进程的运行时间和
when it comes to garbage collection it
说到垃圾收集
can differ a bit between different GCS
在不同的GCS之间可能有所不同
how much they contribute to the total
他们为总数贡献了多少
running time some collectors are going
运行时间一些收藏家要去
to pause so stop the java application
暂停所以停止Java应用程序
and these poses are of course gonna
这些姿势当然会
contribute to the total run time of the
有助于
program but there's also some more
程序，但还有更多
subtle differences Jesus can do
耶稣可以做的细微差别
different optimizations during a pause
暂停期间进行不同的优化
and also while your program is running
以及程序运行时
so different collectors can result in
所以不同的收藏家会导致
shorter or longer total running time for
缩短或延长总运行时间
the same workload and when it comes to
相同的工作量以及涉及的时间
fruit you usually care about that when
水果你通常会在意
you have more
你有更多
pache kind of like workloads for example
例如，pache之类的工作负载
when you compile your java source code
当您编译Java源代码时
with java c you don't really care too
使用Java C您也不太在乎
much how long the JVM is post during the
JVM在发布过程中发布了多长时间
completion you just want your source
完成，您只需要您的来源
code to be compiled as quickly as
代码要尽快编译
possible also you might have offline big
可能你也可能离线很大
data jobs running or you have some
数据作业正在运行，或者您有一些
scientific computation where you're not
您不在的科学计算
really interacting with the program just
真正与程序进行交互
tell to start and you want to get the
告诉开始，你想得到
result back usually we measure this as
结果返回通常我们将其测量为
the again the total running time or the
总的运行时间还是
output during a time unit for example
例如在时间单位内输出
requests per second or something similar
每秒请求数或类似
the second property we're going to talk
我们要谈的第二个属性
about is latency and I will load you in
大约是延迟，我会加载您的
here probably concerned about this
这里大概担心这个
usually this comes up when you have a
通常，当您有一个
service such as a network service we
网络服务等服务
have some back-end service and you have
有一些后端服务，你有
a often you measure the request time so
通常您会评估请求时间，因此
how long if a user wants to see your web
用户希望看到您的网站多长时间
page a long time from that they load the
从他们加载页面很长时间
start low the patient will get a result
从低开始，患者将得到结果
back this is very important and often
回来，这非常重要，而且经常
you see diagram such - - slide where on
你看到这样的图--在哪里滑动
the x-axis you at the time on the y-axis
x轴，您当时的y轴
you have the request time and DC
您有请求时间和DC
contributes this or is a problem when it
促成这一点或当它成为问题时
comes to this because if the garbage
来到这里，因为如果垃圾
collector decides to pause your
收藏家决定暂停您的
application that means it will
应用程序意味着它将
contribute to the request time and
有助于请求时间和
usually when we talk about latency we
通常当我们谈论延迟时
have to think a little bit more than we
必须比我们思考更多
quantify it what we often do is that we
量化它，我们经常做的是，我们
sort the request types from longest to
将请求类型从最长到最大排序
shortest and notice I dropped label on
最短，注意我在标签上放了标签
the x-axis this is just a sort and
在x轴上，这只是一种排序
number of request types now and then we
时不时的请求类型数
can start to quantify what it means
可以开始量化其含义
tell lower or higher later this now we
稍后告诉较低或较高
can say for example well 95% of my
可以说我的95％
requests finished in 50 milliseconds
请求在50毫秒内完成
were shorter and of course we can do the
较短，我们当然可以
same thing when it comes to the garbage
关于垃圾同样的事情
collection process we can measure the GC
收集过程中我们可以测量GC
pauses and note there it's not always
停顿一下，注意并非总是如此
the case that the longest request had
最长的请求的情况
the longest see suppose there are a
最长的看到应该有一个
bunch of other things contributing to
一堆其他有助于
the time of a request there could be
请求的时间可能是
Network latencies they can be io going
他们可能会遇到的网络延迟
on you might have to read something from
关于您可能必须阅读一些内容
disk that contributes but we kind of
磁盘，但我们有点
course do the same thing when it comes
当然，做的事情都是一样的
to GC pauses as will be requests types
到GC暂停，这将是请求类型
we can sort them from longest to
我们可以将它们从最长到最大
shortest and now
现在最短
can start to quantify properties about
可以开始量化关于
our DC post times saying for example
例如，我们的DC发布时间
well 90% of my DC poses were shorter
我的DC姿势中有90％较短
than 10 milliseconds when it comes to
少于10毫秒
latency you often care about that we
延迟，您经常在乎我们
have interactive workloads for example
例如具有交互式工作负载
if you're trying out the new yell tool
如果您正在尝试新的喊工具
in Yeti canine any types of expression
在雪人犬中，任何类型的表达
in the HL you don't want to wait for a
在HL中，您不想等待
long time until you get the answer back
很长一段时间，直到你得到答案
you want to see it immediately and get
您想立即看到它并得到
responsiveness also network services
响应性也网络服务
again a some kind of web back-end you
再次是某种网络后端
care about the requests coming back to
关心返回到的请求
the user quickly and also in graphical
用户也可以以图形方式
applications if you are rendering things
应用程序，如果您正在渲染事物
with a framerate you don't want to frame
以您不想画格的画格
to take to a long time because it will
需要很长时间，因为它将
cause slugging slackness to your
导致你的懈怠
application and when we measure this we
应用程序，当我们测量它时，我们
usually talk a bit about the percentile
通常谈论百分比
of a time unit for example the 95th
时间单位，例如第95
percentile is 50 milliseconds that means
百分位数是50毫秒，这意味着
that 95% won forces were shorter 50
95％的韩军短50
milliseconds and the last properly we're
毫秒和最后一个适当的时间是
gonna see a little bit about is
会看到一点
footprint and here we see a little bit
足迹，在这里我们看到了一点
of an x-ray of a java process going on
正在进行的Java进程的X射线照片
and what contributes to the memory usage
以及什么导致内存使用
of such a java process of course the
这样的Java进程当然
bulk of the memory usage is probably
大量的内存使用情况可能是
going to be the Java heap itself which
将会是Java堆本身
contains lots and lots of Java objects
包含很多Java对象
but there's also other things going on
但是还有其他事情
such the C heap or the native heap that
例如C堆或本机堆
the JVM can use to allocate data
JVM可以用来分配数据
structure it needs to support its
它需要支持其结构
algorithms there might be anonymous
算法可能有匿名
pages mapped in with M map they will of
他们将用M地图映射的页面
course also be gifted code that also
当然也有天赋的代码
takes up space for your process and some
占用您的过程和一些空间
other things going on and when it comes
其他事情正在发生，何时发生
to GC it also contributes to this
对于GC，这也有助于
because different algorithms might
因为不同的算法可能
result in smaller or larger heaps
导致较小或较大的堆
different DC algorithms can also consume
不同的DC算法也会消耗
more or less native memory in order to
或多或少的本机内存以便
support its algorithms and also some
支持它的算法，还有一些
enough pages etc
足够的页面等
and if you are concerned about footprint
如果您担心占地面积
you are probably working in a bit more
你可能还要工作一些
memory constrained environment for
内存受限环境
example you might want to program to run
您可能要编程运行的示例
on a Raspberry Pi and IOT device but
在Raspberry Pi和IOT设备上，但是
it's also starting to sort of become
它也开始变得有点
popular or a frequent problem again when
流行还是经常出现问题
it comes to containers that you want to
它涉及到您想要的容器
pack a lot of JVMs or containers onto a
将很多JVM或容器打包到一个
single machine and we usually measure
单机，我们通常测量
this as the memory usage of a process in
这是一个进程的内存使用量
megabytes or gigabytes so the problem
兆字节或千兆字节，所以问题
here is it is usually hard optimized for
这通常很难进行优化
all this properties at the same time
所有这些属性同时
often you have a trade-off you can
通常，您可以权衡取舍
optimize for one or two of them but then
针对其中一两个进行优化，然后
you will have to sacrifice third one a
你将不得不牺牲第三个
bit sometimes there are some gold
有时有时候会有一些金
optimizations but that is not too common
优化，但不太常见
what's very important is that you define
重要的是您定义
success when it means for your program
对您的程序意味着成功
to perform well in terms of your own
表现出色
application for example if I'm serving
例如，如果我正在提供服务
up a web page then I might say that well
上一个网页，然后我可能会说得很好
all my users visiting a web page or at
我所有访问网页或访问的用户
least 99.9 percent to them should get a
至少有99.9％的人应该得到
web page back in 300 milliseconds or the
网页返回300毫秒或
program should run wrong on a small
程序应该在很小的程度上运行错误
raspberry pi zero or the big day it
覆盆子pi零或重要的一天
knows as the object finish in four hours
知道对象在四个小时内完成
these are properties of your own
这些是你自己的财产
programs no one cares if you have a very
程序没有人在乎，如果你有一个非常
place in a fast JVM but your program
放置在快速的JVM中，但是您的程序
runs slow what's important is that your
运行缓慢，重要的是
program is fast and if that means you
程序很快，如果这意味着你
have the to me a VM that might be it but
给我一台可能是虚拟机的虚拟机，但是
please remember it's all about how the
请记住，这都是关于如何
user perceives the application of your
用户感知到您的应用程序
performance not the JVM itself so we
性能不是JVM本身，所以我们
looked a little bit about these three
看了一下这三个
properties and now we're going to see
属性，现在我们将看到
how we can get some data out of the JVM
我们如何从JVM中获取一些数据
so performance problems can come from
因此性能问题可能来自
any layer in the stack you have your own
您拥有自己的堆栈中的任何一层
application which might have data
可能有数据的应用程序
structures libraries algorithms that
结构库算法
perform sub-optimally the JVM itself of
执行次优的JVM本身
course that is running your application
正在运行您的应用程序的课程
might have problems with the JIT with
可能与JIT有问题
locking with synchronization with GC the
与GC同步锁定
operating system the kernel you might
操作系统，您可能会使用的内核
see problems with schedulers with
查看调度程序的问题
transparent huge pages locking again you
透明的大页面再次锁定您
might have problem with a sealed library
密封库可能有问题
in the user space of your OS that
在操作系统的用户空间中
performs suboptimal a and finally you
执行次优a，最后您
can also of course have problems with
当然也会有问题
the hardware itself may be an outdated
硬件本身可能已过时
firmware that doesn't have all the
没有所有固件
latest performance enhancements there
那里最新的性能增强
might be problems with virtualization
可能是虚拟化的问题
memory bandwidth etc but for this talk
内存带宽等，但在本次演讲中
we're gonna focus on the JVM and
我们将专注于JVM和
particularly the GC but if you really
特别是GC，但如果您真的
want to achieve maximum performance
想要获得最佳性能
you're gonna have to take your whole
你将不得不全力以赴
system into account and look at various
系统考虑并看各种
other things so if we want to know more
其他事情，如果我们想了解更多
about to give them how can we get some
要给他们如何获得一些
data out of it well we have two main
数据很好，我们有两个主要
options here we have Java flight
选项，这里有Java飞行
recorder which is enabled by their flag
通过其标志启用的记录器
- x-axis tower flight recording this
-x轴塔式飞行记录此
will result in a binary recording a
将导致二进制记录
binary format and the you choose which
二进制格式，您可以选择
events you want to subscribe to
您要订阅的活动
subscribe to and get the data that in
订阅并获取其中的数据
the recording and that recording can
录音，该录音可以
later be viewed usually in Java Mission
以后通常在Java Mission中查看
Control you can also use text-based
控制您还可以使用基于文本的
logging in JDK 9 you had the new unified
在JDK 9中登录，您有了新的统一
logging that was introduced behind the
在后面介绍的日志记录
flag - X log the logs are in text format
标志-X日志日志为文本格式
and here when you choose what the kind
在这里，当您选择哪种类型
of data you want to measure you use tags
您要使用标签测量的数据
and levels to describe what information
和级别来描述哪些信息
you want to get out of the JVM and of
您想摆脱JVM和
course these text files can be viewed in
当然这些文本文件可以在
an editorial of your choice and we're
您选择的社论，我们
going to look a bit more deeply into
会更深入地研究
those two options in turn and let's
依次选择这两个选项，让我们
start with Java flight recorder so with
从Java飞行记录器开始
flight recorder today in your k9 you
今天的飞行记录仪在您的K9中
will write java XX unlocked commercial
将编写Java XX解锁的商业广告
features and then start flight recording
功能，然后开始飞行记录
give it a filename recording dot j4 in
给它一个文件名记录点j4
this example and then run your
这个例子，然后运行
application after application is done if
完成申请后，如果
you do LS in the same
你在同一时间做LS
Factory you will find a recording of j4
在工厂，您会发现j4的录音
in there and the recordings the data you
在那里记录数据
get in them or event based issues which
参与其中或基于事件的问题
kind of servants you want to subscribe
您想订阅的那种仆人
to and get that data in the recording
并获取记录中的数据
you can select these events in a JFC
您可以在JFC中选择这些事件
settings file and in JDK 9 you can also
设置文件，在JDK 9中，您还可以
create your own events that is new for
创建自己的新事件
you k 9
你k 9
this is a very powerful feature you can
这是一个非常强大的功能，您可以
create events in your application that
在您的应用程序中创建事件
will end up in the same recording as
最终将与
events from the JVM itself you can
您可以从JVM本身获取事件
correlate maybe you can see that you
相关也许你可以看到你
create an event when you start to do
开始时创建一个事件
your reporting analysis job and you see
您的报告分析工作，您会看到
that when you got that when you also got
当你得到的时候
an event saying that for example the GC
例如说GC的事件
took too long time or etcetera and now
花了太长时间或其他时间，现在
we can very easily correlate between
我们可以很容易地将
these two events happening and see that
这两个事件正在发生，看到
well this was maybe the cost and this
好吧，这也许就是成本，而这
was the effect recordings are viewed in
在观看效果录音时
Java Mission Control or JMC for short
Java Mission Control或JMC的简称
JMC 6.0 was released alongside Oracle
JMC 6.0与Oracle一起发布
JDK 9 and you can use your emission
JDK 9，您可以使用您的发射
control to start recording so you don't
控制开始录制，这样您就不必
have to use the command line you can use
必须使用您可以使用的命令行
the MC to get the recordings going you
MC来获取录音
can also in JMC configure which events
也可以在JMC中配置哪些事件
you want to get data from and in
您想从中获取数据
starting in games is six you will also
从游戏开始六点钟
get automatic analysis your recordings
自动分析您的录音
so JMC as a rules engine that can did
因此，JMC是可以做到的规则引擎
use what has been going on based on the
使用基于
events in the recording and if you want
记录中的事件以及是否需要
more information see oracle calm /
更多信息，请参见oracle /
Mission Control for more details about
任务控制有关的更多详细信息
JMC and here's a screenshot showing what
JMC和下面的屏幕快照显示了
James it looks like when we look a bit
詹姆斯，当我们看起来有点像
more into detail at the garbage
更详细地介绍了垃圾
collection information logging the other
收集信息记录另一个
choice for getting data out of the JVM
从JVM提取数据的选择
so JDK 9 introduced a new flag - X log
因此JDK 9引入了一个新标志-X日志
and the unified logging framework so the
和统一的日志记录框架
format for the options to enable logging
用于启用日志记录的选项的格式
is in simplified form - X log is like a
是简化形式-X日志就像一个
tag you select which level you want
标记您选择想要的级别
information on the tag and you tell log
标签上的信息，您告诉日志
in subsystem where the log should end up
在子系统中日志应该结束的地方
on esterday out a city or arena file
在esterday出城或竞技场档案
perhaps for an example here on the slide
也许是幻灯片上的一个例子
we see that I want for all messages
我们看到我想要所有消息
tagged with DC I want the info level on
标记为DC的信息级别
those if the or messages tagged with DC
如果或消息标记有DC
plus faces
加脸
I want the debug level on dos and for
我想要在dos和上的调试级别
safe
安全
almost
几乎
just tagged with safepoint I want them
刚刚标记了安全点，我想要他们
on the trace level and I want all this
在跟踪级别上，我想要所有这些
in the file GZ - logo text for more
在文件GZ中-更多徽标文字
details on this command line flags and
有关此命令行标志的详细信息以及
how to specify the syntax you can see
如何指定可以看到的语法
Jack 158 on open a decade of java.net
杰克158开启java.net十年
slash slash 158 and for an example what
斜杠158，例如
output looks from a log here I'm just
从这里的日志输出看起来只是
enabling GC and since the fourth level
从第四级开始启用GC
is info I will now get one messages
是信息，我现在将收到一条消息
tagged with GC on the info level and
在信息级别上用GC标记，并且
then you also run your application and
然后您还运行您的应用程序
to start out we see that for each line I
首先，我们看到每一行
get a few decorations so the first
得到一些装饰，所以第一个
columns or in this case you get a
列，在这种情况下，您会得到一个
timestamp when was this log message
此日志消息的时间戳记
written you will see the level so I'm
写你会看到水平，所以我
running with the default level which is
以默认级别运行
info so all my lines have the info level
信息，所以我所有的行都有信息级别
I'm also getting logs that are tagged
我也得到了带有标签的日志
with GC and only GC so here I'm getting
与GC和只有GC，所以在这里
C which tags this message hasn't of
C此消息没有标签的
course only GC and then the message
当然只GC，然后消息
itself and here the JVM is telling you
本身，JVM在这里告诉你
that you are now running with g1 looking
你现在正在用g1运行
into a bit more what a G suppose looks
更像G的样子
like on this kind of logging level you
就像在这种日志记录级别上
again see the timestamp the info level
再次查看时间戳信息级别
the GC tag and then we come into the
GC标签，然后我们进入
actual log message and for each log
实际日志消息以及每个日志
message you will get a GC ID here for
消息，您将在此处获得GC ID
the first one is 0 they don't have to
第一个是0，他们不必
come in consecutive order it is just an
以连续的顺序来只是一个
identifier because we will see later
标识符，因为我们稍后会看到
there might be more log lines for a
可能会有更多的日志行
single GC and then the ID helps you to
单个GC，然后ID可以帮助您
identify which lines belong to which
识别哪些线属于
garbage collection posts it tells you
垃圾收集帖子告诉你
what kind of post this was this was a
这是什么样的帖子
young post apparently and we will see
年轻的职位显然，我们将看到
where that is the reason for the post
那是该职位的原因
this was a recreation post the heap
这是堆的娱乐场所
usage before the post after the post and
发帖前的用法发帖后和
the capacity how much memory could have
容量可能有多少内存
grown too and the thing was to your
也长大了，这是给你的
concern about the length of the post
关注帖子的长度
itself alright so we looked at how to
本身很好，所以我们研究了如何
get data order JVM and do some
获取数据顺序JVM并执行一些操作
measurements now let's get in a little
现在让我们开始测量
bit more into tuning so tuning often
多一点调整，所以经常调整
starts with a problem that you are
从你的问题开始
noticing maybe a request took too long
注意到请求可能花费了太长时间
time when you had in your performance
表演的时间
lab you discover that the CPU of one
实验室，您发现一个CPU
your service is hundred
你的服务一百
and utilized or the Java process
和利用或Java流程
throughout the memory you need to
整个内存中，您需要
understand why and what happened and
了解为什么和发生了什么，以及
what is going on in there
那里发生了什么
so in all these cases I usually apply
所以在所有这些情况下，我通常都会申请
the method of first I measure to see
我先看一下的方法
what has been going on then I need to
发生了什么事，那么我需要
understand why was this happening and
了解为什么会这样，并且
when we have the data and we have an
当我们有数据，我们有一个
understanding of the problem they're
了解他们所面临的问题
making often tune around it and so the
经常在它周围调音，所以
issue but first things first
发出但先要先
when you start the queue and start to
当您开始排队并开始
measure you want to optimize something
测量您想要优化的东西
use a minimal number of Aeon Flux to
使用最少数量的Aeon Flux
begin with we see many examples where
首先，我们看到许多例子
people have been inheriting previous
人们一直在继承以前
colleagues JVM flags for years maybe in
多年的同事JVM标志可能在
their fifth generation there are so many
他们的第五代有很多
flags in there most of them might not
其中的大多数标记可能不会
even apply any longer there might be
甚至不再使用
conflicting flags flags for different
不同的冲突标志标志
kind of garbage collection in the same
一样的垃圾收集
command line so just start out with X MX
命令行，因此只需从X MX开始
to begin with get a clean fresh slate
首先要获得干净的新鲜石板
when you starting to optimize please
当您开始优化时，请
rely on first hand after it information
依靠第一手资料
for yet ek9 and my colleague Thomas just
对于ek9和我的同事Thomas
rewrote the entire g1 tuning guidelines
重写了整个g1调整准则
so they are freshly rewritten for 9 with
所以他们被重新改写为9
all the latest info so please have a
所有最新信息，所以请
look at that document and much of this
看那个文件，还有很多
presentation is of course based on this
演示当然基于此
it will help you out when you are tuning
当您调音时它将帮助您
again g1 has been around for a long time
再次g1已经存在很长时间了
there are much outdated information on
关于许多过时的信息
the web in various blogs talks etc so
各种博客讨论中的网络等等
please use up-to-date information when
请在以下情况使用最新信息
you start attune and finally use as
您开始调音，最后用作
recent JDK as possible this is
最近的JDK可能是
particularly important for g1 which has
对于具有
improved a lot in more recent years a
近年来有了很大的进步a
releases alright so the problem we're
发布好了，所以我们的问题
gonna look at today is too long poses
今天要看的姿势太长了
this is often what we hear from users
这通常是我们从用户那里听到的
that they are concerned about and want
他们关心并想要的
to tune and again why do we care about
再次调整，为什么我们会关心
this well if you have some kind of
如果你有某种
interact application and the JVM and in
交互应用程序和JVM
GC this case poses your application you
GC这种情况给您提出了申请
will have longer requests times or you
将会有更长的请求时间，否则您
will drop frames etc so we want to
会丢帧等，所以我们想
shorten these poses in for interactive
缩短这些姿势以进行互动
applications your first go to a flag
申请您​​的第一个标志
here is going to be
这将是
Maxie supports Millis because this is
Maxie支持Millis，因为这是
the flag that in many cases drives D
在许多情况下驱动D的标志
ones or economics engines so Jiwon tries
或经济引擎，所以智元尝试
to keep a post target and this postdoc
保持职位目标和本博士后
is 200 milliseconds by default if you
如果您默认设置为200毫秒
increase this post target and you give
增加这个职位目标，你给
the higher value let's say I'm fine with
较高的价值，可以说我很好
500 millisecond pulses that means you
500毫秒脉冲意味着您
will get more fruit put out of your
会从你身上拿出更多的水果
application but you will also get higher
申请，但您还会得到更高
latencies because you are saying I'm
延迟，因为你是说我
fine with 500 millisecond posters and if
罚款500毫秒海报，如果
you're fine with that in turn you will
你会没事的，你会
get better throughput on the other hand
另一方面获得更好的吞吐量
if you say that I want really short
如果你说我要很短
pauses then you can decrease this value
暂停然后您可以降低此值
to for example 100 milliseconds or 80
到例如100毫秒或80
milliseconds that of course comes with a
当然会附带一个毫秒
cost
成本
there again these trade-offs always show
这些权衡总是表明
up as you will get less Rupert but on
上升，因为您得到的Rupert会减少，但是
the other hand you will also get shorter
另一方面，你也会变矮
poses but what if setting max DC for
摆姿势，但是如果将最大DC设置为
smelliest isn't enough you set it to the
最臭的还不够，您将其设置为
value you want here I'm running with 200
您要在这里值200我正在运行
default but still these poses seems to
默认但这些姿势似乎仍然
be a bit too long we have one at 220 170
有点太久了，我们有一个220 170
and then we have a really slow one at
然后我们有一个非常慢的
400 the first thing I look into is what
400我首先要看的是什么
kind of force is this because you need
这种力量是因为你需要
to understand in order to solve this
为了解决这个问题而了解
problems we must understand what's going
问题，我们必须了解发生了什么
on otherwise we ask on a guest us at a
否则我们会请客人在
bunch of JVM Flags trying randomly after
一堆JVM标志在之后随机尝试
something seems to work and that won't
有些东西似乎有效，那将不会
lead to any good so again start looking
导致任何好处，所以再次开始寻找
at the kind of post here we see a few
在这里的帖子中，我们看到了一些
different kinds of forces we apparently
我们显然有不同的力量
have one Yan pose one mixed post and one
有一个燕姿势一个混合职位和一个
full pose and we're going to look at
完整的姿势，我们将要看
them in turn and see what we can do
他们反过来看看我们能做什么
about these problems so to begin with we
关于这些问题，所以从我们开始
will see a little bit more about the
会看到更多关于
joint poses and this young post
联合姿势和这个年轻的职位
apparently run for a bit too long to
显然运行了太长时间
other 20 milliseconds compared to 200
其他20毫秒，而200毫秒
and they weren't the soleus problem we
他们不是我们的比目鱼问题
must remember the steps first we measure
必须先记住我们测量的步骤
and we have measured and gotten a date
我们已经测量并确定了一个日期
out then we need to understand why is
然后我们需要了解为什么
this happening what is going on inside
这发生了什么事
the JVM when we have this knowledge we
JVM当我们掌握了这些知识后，
can tune around the problem but do we
可以解决问题，但是我们可以
have sufficient aid in this case or do
在这种情况下有足够的帮助或
we know enough no I don't think so we
我们知道的不，我不认为，所以我们
need to know a bit mobile young
需要知道一点流动青年
connectionist and what is going on so g1
连接主义者，这是怎么回事g1
splits the heap into multiple regions
将堆分成多个区域
you have Eden regions and survival
你有伊甸园地区和生存
regions this
地区这
come together known as young regions
一起被称为青年地区
there will be free witness on the heap
堆上会有免费的见证人
with no objects inside them
里面没有物体
River also the old regions an object
河水也是老区的一个对象
stores out by being allocated into an
通过分配到
Eden region then after as it a John
伊甸园地区后来成为约翰
collection happens and it survives a
收集发生并且可以生存
giant collection it will be copied into
巨大的收藏将被复制到
a survival region and if it survives
一个生存区域，如果生存
multiple yarn collections it will
它将收集多个纱线
eventually end up being promoted into an
最终被提升为
old region looking at the heap prior to
在看堆之前的旧区域
a giant collection you see that all of
庞大的收藏，您会发现
our Eden regions have objects inside
我们的伊甸园地区里面有物体
them and also the survival region the
他们以及生存地区
orange objects are live those are the
橙色物体是活的，那些是
ones that are actually in use so g1 will
实际使用中的，因此g1将
find this orange objects in the ether
在乙醚中找到这个橙色的物体
and survival reaches the live ones and
生存到达了活着的
it will compactly copy them into a free
它将紧凑地复制到一个免费的
region and update all the references so
区域并更新所有参考，以便
that the world looks sane again when the
当世界再次变得理智
jvm when the job application resumes so
作业申请恢复时的JVM
f is for a free region so we copy the
f是自由区域，因此我们复制
compactly copy the live objects into a
将活动对象紧凑地复制到
free region and afterwards when is
自由区域，之后何时是
copying is done we will as a result
复制完成，我们将因此
havin the free region turn into a
将自由区域变成一个
survival region and the Eden regions
生存区和伊甸园地区
turn into three regions and can be once
变成三个区域，可以一次
again used for allocations as you see we
再次用于分配，如您所见
started out with one free region and
从一个自由区域开始
have a compactly copied four regions
紧凑地复制了四个区域
into one free region and now we have
进入一个自由区域，现在我们有了
four free regions so we have the heap is
四个空闲区域，所以我们拥有的堆是
more dense more compact so we can reuse
更密集，更紧凑，因此我们可以重复使用
the memory for new allocations so
新分配的内存，因此
looking at this posts we now have
看这个帖子，我们现在有
understanding of what is going on a bit
了解发生了什么
more and tirion collection but do we
更多和提里奥收集，但我们
have enough data no in this case we
没有足够的数据，在这种情况下，我们
don't so we need to enable more logging
否，所以我们需要启用更多日志记录
and now I'm going to say - X log G store
现在我要说的是-X log G store
that means I want to lag log all tags
这意味着我要滞后记录所有标签
that's including at IDC so there might
这包括在IDC中，所以可能
be log messages including GC but also
是包括GC的日志消息，而且
other tags and now I want all the lines
其他标签，现在我想要所有行
with GC and potentially other tags
带有GC和其他可能的标签
inside them so let's see what we get
在他们里面，让我们看看我们得到了什么
when we do easy store Wow now we got a
当我们做简单的商店哇，现在我们有一个
lot more information and here we can see
更多信息，在这里我们可以看到
that DC ID helps us out by so we can see
DC ID可以帮助我们，因此我们可以看到
which lines belongs to which garbage
哪些行属于哪个垃圾
collection and these all belong to GC
集合，这些都属于GC
154 we can see we still have the John
154我们可以看到我们还有约翰
Force
力
where
哪里
thing apparently 18 workers for this
事情显然为此18名工人
evacuation so things are being run a lot
疏散，所以事情很多
in parallel with their different faces
与他们不同的面孔平行
apparently we have the pre evacuated
显然，我们已经预先疏散了
collection set evacuated collection set
集合集撤离的集合集
and post evacuate accept and then some
然后撤离后接受，然后一些
other time we can see the radiant
其他时候我们可以看到辐射
distribution prior to the collection
收集之前分发
after collection so we had three hundred
收集后，我们有三百
and fourteen in the region's prior to
和该区域之前的14个
junk collection and as we now know to
垃圾收集，现在我们知道
eat in radiance we will compactly copy
吃光彩，我们会紧凑地复制
the objects into three regions so there
这些物体分为三个区域
are sierra ones afterwards they have all
后来都是塞拉利昂人
become free we had thirty four survival
变得自由，我们有34个生存时间
regions going on today going into the
今天要去的地区
collection and when we were done the
收集以及完成后
data resided in 32 survival regions and
数据位于32个生存区域，
the old radiance increased from four
旧的光辉从四个增加
hundred fifteen to four hundred forty
一百十五至四百四十
nine
九
we also got the information about the
我们还获得了有关
among students i'm at a space we will
在学生中，我在一个空间中
not go into that today and finally we
今天不谈那个，最后我们
get the heap usage before and after the
获取之前和之后的堆使用情况
capacity and the time for the post
职位的能力和时间
itself so if we look a bit more closely
本身，所以如果我们仔细观察一下
here we see that it seems like this face
在这里，我们看到这张脸
evacuate collection set takes almost all
撤离集合几乎需要全部
the time we see it took fifty two point
我们看到的时间花了52分
five milliseconds out of 54 we also see
54毫秒中有5毫秒
that there seems to be quite an increase
似乎增加了
in old regions and we're also using
在旧的地区，我们也在使用
quite a bit of survival regions so again
相当多的生存区域
evacuating collection set took time
撤离收藏集需要时间
there was a proximate in ninety seventy
九十年代有一个近邻
percent of the post man helped make seem
职位员的百分比帮助使人显得
to survive we had to use thirty four new
为了生存，我们必须使用34个新的
algorithms and forty two new survival
算法和四十二个新的生存
regions but to really get to the bottom
区域，但要真正触底
this we need even more information to
我们需要更多的信息来
finally see what happened here so we're
终于看到这里发生了什么，所以我们
gonna enable debug level on all log
将在所有日志上启用调试级别
lines including the tide GC so let's see
包括潮汐GC在内的各行，让我们来看一下
what we get we're gonna get a lot of
我们得到的我们会得到很多
output this is not something you wanna
输出这不是你想要的东西
run in production you will quickly fill
在生产中运行，您将快速填充
up to log to a lot of info but if you're
记录很多信息，但是如果您是
tuning and drilling down into a specific
调优并深入到特定
problem this might work will help you
问题，这可能会有所帮助
and so i just copy the part of the log
所以我只复制日志的一部分
here there are a bunch more information
这里有一堆更多的信息
about the GC but now we will see all the
关于GC，但现在我们将看到所有
phases under sub phases listed in the
相中列出的子相下的相
log and we will see that the face that
日志，我们将看到那张脸
took a lot of time was OB copy and now
花了很多时间是OB复制，现在
you see the face is labeled with mean
你看到那张脸标有意思
average max that's because all this is
这是因为所有这些的最大平均值
being run in parallel and concurrent at
在并行和并发运行
the same time so the average time a
因此，平均时间是
worker spent you doing
工人花你做
it was for approximately four to nine
大约是四到九点
milliseconds and the most time worker
毫秒和最多时间的工作人员
took was fifty minutes again so
又花了五十分钟，所以
apparently the post is spent doing OB
显然，该职位是花在做OB
copy so what can we conclude well
复制，那么我们能得出什么很好的结论
copying objects takes time but why the G
复制对象需要时间，但为什么G
one has two copies so many objects for
一个有两个副本，所以有很多对象
this pose well most objects are supposed
这个姿势很好，大多数物体都应该
most young objects or supposed to be
最年轻的物体或应该是
dead and this is based on the hypothesis
死了，这是基于假设
that most objects either die young or
大多数物体要么早逝，要么死亡
they live for a very long time if this
他们如果活了很长时间
is not true free application you might
不是真正的免费应用程序
have to tune the number of John regions
必须调整约翰地区的数量
that you one can use you might have set
你可以使用的你可能已经设定
the flag CG one new size present in g1
g1中出现的标志CG一个新尺寸
max new size percent perhaps you have
最大新尺寸百分比，也许您有
more information about your application
有关您的应用程序的更多信息
than g1 can deduce because I ergonomics
比g1可以推断出来，因为我的工效学
engines will try to find an optimum
引擎将尝试找到最佳选择
value here but you might know something
在这里很有价值，但您可能会知道一些
that you want duster for example you
你想要want子
know I'm going to generate a big big
知道我会产生很大的变化
report or something and once the report
报告或其他内容，一旦报告
is done all the basic cannot die but if
完成所有基本的工作就不会死，但是如果
g1 decides to pause before the report is
g1决定在报表生成之前暂停
done
完成
there might below a live objects around
下面可能有一个活物
that has to be copied also if you just
如果您只是要复制
increase the number of John regions a
增加约翰地区的数量
bit the objects will have more time to
一点物体将有更多时间
die and it will be less live objects
死亡，将减少活物
Fuji want to copy moving on we will have
富士想复制前进，我们将
a little look at a mixed pose and the
稍微看看混合姿势
good thing here is that you will now
好东西是你现在
have a better understanding of young
对年轻人有更好的了解
collections you can bring that knowledge
您可以带来这些知识的收藏
over into mixed collections because they
进入混合收藏，因为它们
are very very similar the difference is
非常非常相似，区别是
that a mixed collection collects both
混合收集同时收集
young and old regions and as we've
年轻人和老年人地区以及我们
already seen the young regions can be
已经见过的年轻地区可以
all disappear
全部消失
the young readings can be bounded with
年轻的读物可能会受到限制
g1 max new size percent but what about
g1最大新大小百分比，但是
the old regions can you bound the number
旧的地区你可以绑定数字吗
of old regions in a pose we need to
我们需要摆姿势的旧区域
understand a bit more about mixed
了解更多有关混合的信息
collections in order to answer a
为了回答一个集合
question so if you look at this heap on
问题，所以如果你看看这个堆
the slide here we have a bunch of eden
幻灯片在这里，我们有一堆伊甸园
regions with orange level between them
它们之间为橙色水平的区域
we have two old regions into three
我们将两个旧区域分为三个
regions and the old radius was a few
地区和旧半径是一些
live orange objects what you want to do
橙色物体的活动
for a mixed collection is going to
混合收藏
select all the young regions those are
选择所有的年轻地区
even a survivor once they always had to
即使是幸存者，一旦他们总是不得不
be
是
collecting opposed and one or more old
收集对立的和一个或多个旧的
regions and definitely do the same thing
地区，并且肯定会做同样的事情
as in a giant collection the live
就像一个巨大的收藏
objects would be compactly copied into
对象将被紧凑地复制到
three regions and then the regions in
三个区域，然后是
this and then the old radians and
这个，然后是老弧度，
younghui s that were collected will
收集的杨辉
become free regions so again very
成为自由地区，所以再次
similar the code is actually almost the
类似的代码实际上几乎是
same for a young and a mixed collection
对于年轻和混合的收藏也是如此
so g1 selects a collection set of
因此g1选择了一个集合集
regions we can bound the junk part of
我们可以绑定的垃圾部分的区域
the collection set with g1 max new size
g1最大新大小的收藏集
% and we can bound the old part with g1
％，我们可以用g1绑定旧部分
mix GC count target g1 mix this account
混合GC计数目标g1混合此帐户
target is by default 8 and that means
目标默认为8，这意味着
that Jia will strive to collect all old
贾将努力收集所有旧的
regions during 8 mix collections if
8个混合集合中的区域，如果
you're looking for lower latencies this
您正在寻找更低的延迟时间
might be a way to low value let's say
也许是一种低价值的方法
you have 800 old regions because they
您有800个旧区域，因为它们
were rather large heap and you want to
堆很大，你想
achieve short poses you don't want to
摆出你不想的姿势
copy a little data each post you want to
您想要复制每个帖子一些数据
spread the work out during many mix
在许多混合中分散工作
collections well if you have 800 old
如果您有800个旧的收藏
regions and you have a mix GC contract
地区，您有一份混合GC合同
of 8 you might end up with approximately
之八，您可能会得到大约
100 old regions permits collection if
100个旧区域允许收集
most of regions are rather full and this
大部分地区都比较饱满
can be way too many you see two way to
可能太多了，您会看到两种方法
long process and then it's a good sign
漫长的过程，这是一个好兆头
you might have to increase mix GC count
您可能需要增加混合GC计数
target to a higher value you can also
定位到更高的价值，您也可以
tell you one that it doesn't have to do
告诉你一个不必做
so much which seems a bit strange but
这么多，似乎有点奇怪，但
you can soon it to do less work with the
您可以尽快减少与
flags for example mix GC live threshold
标志，例如mix GC活动阈值
percent which by default is 85 and this
百分比，默认情况下是85，
flags would tell g1 went to consider
标志会告诉g1去考虑
collecting an old region because if a
收集旧区域，因为如果
region is mostly filled with live
该地区主要是现场直播
objects and then we just kind of shuffle
对象，然后我们只是随机播放
data around on the heap we're going to
堆中的数据
move objects there are one was old and
移动物体有一个是旧的
live from one region to another so on
从一个地区生活到另一个地区，依此类推
the slides we haven't really gained
我们还没有真正获得的幻灯片
anything I mean the point of all these
任何我想说的都是这些
collections is to collect multiple
集合是要收集多个
regions with a few live all between them
他们之间生活着几个地区
into one single region so we can reuse
分成一个区域，这样我们就可以重复使用
the other regions but if a region is
其他区域，但如果一个区域是
almost full now we won't really get much
现在快要满了
monomer back and g1 mix dive yeah do you
单体背和g1混合潜水是吗
want mix this is like threshold % tells
要混合，就像阈值％告诉
g1 the threshold who ran to consider
g1可以考虑的阈值
collecting an old region and by default
收集旧区域，默认情况下
that is 85% full if you decrease this
如果减少此数量，则已满85％
value that means that g1 will skip
表示g1将跳过的值
collecting if said 65 percent or 55
如果说65％或55，则收集
percent then g1 will skip collecting
则g1将跳过收集
those old regions but this might result
那些古老的地区，但这可能会导致
in more heap usage we're going to leave
在更多的堆使用中，我们将离开
more garbage lying around on the heap
更多的垃圾躺在堆上
the other flag is g1 heap waste percent
另一个标志是g1堆浪费百分比
which almost as well means in name which
这几乎也意味着名字
allows more garbage on the heap so this
允许堆上有更多垃圾，所以这
is a goal for g1
是g1的目标
it says that I'm okay with leaving by
它说我可以离开
default 5% of garbage lying around on
默认情况下5％的垃圾散落在
the heap if you are ok with more garbage
如果还可以的话，堆更多的垃圾
on the heap that means that even can do
在堆上，这意味着甚至可以做
less work and you can increase this
减少工作量，您可以增加它
value but again a warning this will
值，但再次警告这将
result in more heap usage and again we
导致更多的堆使用，我们再次
start to see this trade of you we got
开始看到你的这种交易
shorter poses but perhaps more footprint
较短的姿势，但可能会占用更多的空间
alright we saved the worst one for last
好吧，我们挽救了最糟糕的一个
so here we see a full clip pose and
所以在这里我们看到一个完整的剪辑姿势，
apparently this took way wait a long
显然这花了很长时间
time if a typo story of 200 we are up at
时间是200的错字故事
400 here so this doesn't seem too good
400这里，这似乎不太好
what is going on here if you see a full
如果看到一个完整的，这是怎么回事
collection that's a bad sign they are
这是一个不好的迹象
not supposed to happen this is a failure
不应该发生，这是一个失败
mode of d1 and it is clearly not running
d1模式，显然没有运行
optimally it is very important for you
最理想的是对您来说很重要
to understand why a full collection
了解为什么要完整收集
happened the good news is that it's
发生的好消息是
often pretty easy to find out where full
通常很容易找出哪里充满
collection happen and work around it but
收集发生并解决它，但是
it's very important that you do it if a
如果一个
full collection shows up in your log or
完整的收藏会显示在您的日志中，或
in your day for recording you need to
在您录制的那一天，您需要
gather understanding of what was going
收集对正在发生的事情的了解
on because this is again a failure mode
亮，因为这又是一种失败模式
so in the log you will see the posts
所以在日志中，您将看到帖子
here the full post at the bottom bolded
底部的完整文章以粗体显示
if you just look a little bit earlier
如果你只是早一点看
into the previous lines you will notice
进入前几行，您会注意到
this little line in the previous john
前约翰的这句话
collection to space exhausted what could
收集到太空用尽了什么
that mean well during a John collection
这意味着在约翰收藏期间
as we've seen g1 will try to compactly
正如我们所见，g1将尝试紧凑
copy all the live objects into a free
将所有活动对象复制到免费
region well what is a lower of live
该地区的生活水平较低
objects in the young regions and not
对象在年轻地区而不是
that many free regions left on the heap
堆上还有那么多空闲区域
well we will get a to space exhauster
好吧，我们将得到一个太空人
that means that the war
那意味着战争
that much space to copy the live objects
复制活动对象的空间
into so instead the the Eden regions and
因此，伊甸园地区和
the incoming survival regions will just
即将到来的生存地区将只是
be turned into old regions we won't
变成我们不会的旧地区
almost free up any memory and as a
几乎释放了所有内存，并且
result we will eventually pretty soon
结果我们最终会很快
after run into a full collection and
遇到完整的收藏后，
here come out ask yourself what I didn't
出来问你自己我没做什么
even do a mixed collection here I mean
我什至在这里做一个混合的收藏
if we look again there were a couple of
如果我们再看一次，有几个
old regions there couldn't we have
那里的老城区我们不能
collected a few of them freed up some
收集了一些，释放了一些
memory and reuse that we must understand
我们必须了解的内存和重用
a bit more about g1 to answer a question
关于g1的更多回答问题
I understand what we didn't do what we
我了解我们没有做什么
did a junk collection and not an old
做了一个垃圾收集，而不是一个旧的
collection or mixed collection so on the
收集或混合收集等
previous slides we've seen only just
以前的幻灯片我们只看过
vaguely hinted at well there's going to
隐约暗示好了
be this orange live object but never
是这个橙色的活物，但永远不会
really told you why they are there how
真的告诉你为什么他们在那里
did you even find out what was live and
你甚至发现了生活是什么，
what wasn't live so J one finds live
什么不是活着，所以J人找到了活着
objects in young regions every time it
每次都在年轻地区的物体
does a giant collection there are
是否有一个巨大的收藏
usually a few live objects in the jungle
通常在丛林中有一些活物
region so this is pretty quick and it's
地区，所以这是非常快的
done during a force however for the old
但是，对于旧的
regions of which are often plenty g1
经常有很多g1的地区
we'll concurrently find all our objects
我们将同时找到所有对象
and this can is called concurrent
这可以称为并发
marking and can take a bit of time
标记，可能需要一些时间
especially if you have a large heap and
特别是如果你有一大堆
the good news is that this will not stop
好消息是，这不会停止
your job application this is running
您的求职申请正在运行
concurrently at the same time as the job
与工作同时进行
application is running but the problem
应用程序正在运行，但是问题
is that Jamin cannot collect a region
是贾明无法收集一个地区
without lightness information if doesn't
没有亮度信息，如果没有
know which objects are live or dead it
知道哪些物体是活的还是死的
can't know which space to reclaim so
不知道要回收哪个空间
mixed connections require concurrent
混合连接需要并发
mark to finish and why is that a problem
标记完成，为什么会出现问题
let's have a look at an example so as
让我们看一个例子
your application starts out you will
您的应用程序启动后，您将
allocate objects into Eden regions as
将对象分配给伊甸地区
you allocate more and more you're going
你分配越来越多，你要去
to start to fill up more and more
开始填充越来越多
ingredients and d1 will decide up now
成分和d1现在决定
it's a good time to pause you have
现在是暂停你的好时机
filled up quite a few million regions
充满了数百万个地区
and your young collections it will find
还有你的年轻收藏
all the young live objects during that
在那期间所有年轻的活物
post it will compactly cop them into
发布它会紧凑地将它们放入
surviving as we have seen and as you
如我们所见和您一样生存
guess here on a timeline this is a
在时间轴上猜这是一个
little post where your application is
您的应用程序所在的小职位
post and I will continue running
发布，我将继续运行
now as time goes on more and more of
随着时间的流逝，越来越多的
these young collections will occur and
这些年轻的收藏将会出现，
eventually objects we start to survive
最终我们开始生存的对象
more and more young collections and will
越来越多的年轻收藏，并将
be promoted into old radiance again time
再次被提升到旧的光彩
continues more and more pauses and now
持续不断的停顿，现在
the old regions are starting to fill up
旧的地区开始充满
as well but from g1 point of view they
同样，但从g1的角度来看
are being filled up with like objects
被满满的东西
believers can't really tell the
信徒们真的不能说
difference at this point about the live
关于现场直播的不同之处
in the Adobe Act in an old region now
现在在旧区域的Adobe Act中
it's a good time to start the coherent
现在是开始连贯的好时机
mark because we need the concurrent mark
标记，因为我们需要并发标记
to finish before we run out of free
在我们用尽免费之前完成
regions on the heap so here you can see
堆上的区域，所以在这里您可以看到
that the concurrent threads are kicked
并发线程被踢
off on the time axis and it's being run
在时间轴上关闭并且正在运行
at the same time as the vacation is
在假期的同时
running so there's no pause in there
运行，所以那里没有暂停
there might be young collections going
可能会有年轻的收藏
on concurrently really concurrent
在并发上
marking that is perfectly fine and these
标记非常好，这些
giant collections might promote more and
庞大的收藏可能会促进更多的发展，
more objects into old radians so now
更多的物体变成旧弧度，所以现在
it's getting rather heat full-dome and
全场热越来越大，
hopefully concurrent mark is about to
希望并发标记即将
finish soon so we can reclaim memory
即将完成，以便我们可以回收内存
from old regions and luckily enough it
来自旧地区，幸运的是
just finished so now that concurrent
刚刚完成，所以现在并发
mark finished jeeva finally gets the
马克·吉娃（jeeva）完蛋了
liveness information it needs and
它需要的活动信息，以及
discovers aha there were only a few of
发现啊哈，只有几个
the Excel of in each old region and if
每个旧区域的Excel，如果
we go back to our problematic post that
我们回到有问题的帖子
was very long we saw at the bottom we
很长时间，我们在底部看到
have the long full post it notification
有长时间的完整发布通知
failure we look a bit further up we saw
失败，我们再往前看
the two basic sauce hood okay they
两个基本的油烟机好吧，他们
weren't enough survival regions for a
没有足够的生存区域
yarn collection to co-publishing to and
纱线收藏要共同发布到
if we look even further up we see that
如果我们进一步向上看，我们会看到
oh there was a concurrent cycle started
哦，并发周期开始了
and concurrent mark was kicked off but
并发标记开始了，但是
the important thing here is what we do
重要的是我们要做的
not see in the log we should we do not
在日志中看不到，我们应该不要
see at the concurrent cycle finished
并发周期看完
concurrent mark did not have time to
并发标记没有时间
finish it didn't finish in time the g1
完成它没有按时完成g1
couldn't get the lioness information it
无法获得母狮信息
needed to collect old regions and
需要收集旧地区和
therefore when they were no more free
因此，当他们不再自由时
readings available it had to fall back
可用的读数必须回落
to the failure mode a full collection in
到故障模式下的完整集合
Gaelic nine we introduced adaptive sort
盖尔九我们引入了自适应排序
of concurrent cycle this means that we
并发周期，这意味着我们
will driven by the data we gathered
将由我们收集的数据驱动
during run time of your application how
在您的应用程序运行时如何
it behaves and our policies we will the
它的行为和我们的政策，我们将
kickoff the concurrent mark threads
启动并发标记线程
hopefully in time this is driven by the
希望这是由
economics and
经济学和
but you might say that I'm really
但你可能会说我真的
concerned about this I really want to
对此我真的很想
finish in time so you can if increase g1
及时完成，所以如果增加g1
reserve percent which is by default 10
保留百分比，默认为10
to say that okay I know that you can
说好吧，我知道你可以
calculate fairly well when to store in
计算得很好，何时存储
car markets but please have a buffer at
汽车市场，但请留意
the end of three regions so that you
三个区域的末端，以便您
really do finish in time and if
确实确实按时完成，如果
something happens during a card marking
卡片标记期间发生了某些事情
for example you get your blog post on
例如，您在以下位置获得博客文章
Hockey News and suddenly you have a too
曲棍球新闻，突然之间你也有
many visitors to your website and a lot
您网站的访问者很多，很多
of objects are being allocated as a
的对象被分配为
result you might need a little bit
结果你可能需要一点
slightly larger buffer you can also
稍大的缓冲区，您也可以
increase the heap size to give
增加堆大小
concurrent marking more Headroom and
同时标记更多的净空和
more time to finish as it traverses the
遍历
heap it is very important that if you do
堆非常重要，如果您这样做
get a full collection as you analyze not
不进行分析就得到完整的收藏
only why it happened but also the
只是为什么会发生，而且
outcome of that photo collection
该照片集的结果
particularly if the full collection
特别是如果完整的收藏
didn't free up any memory that means
没有释放任何内存，这意味着
that either the heap is too small or
要么堆太小，要么
rather you have a too large number of
而是你有太多的
live objects for heap without size or
没有大小的堆的活动对象
you might have a memory leak in your
您可能在您的内存泄漏
application filling up the heap we all
应用程序填满了我们所有人
be student villi but you are some how
是学生绒毛，但你有些
holding on to them looking in Java
坚持他们在Java中寻找
Mission Control here we see an example
任务控制在这里我们看到一个例子
of automated analysis introduced in
引入的自动化分析
James's 6.0 and we see that the full
詹姆斯的6.0，我们看到了完整
collections get a full 100 severity
集合的严重程度为100
score that means that this is a serious
分数意味着这是严重的
problem and it also says the g1 garbage
问题，它也说g1垃圾
collection will use but the JVM too
集合将使用，但JVM也将使用
diverse here old collection and we see
这里的旧收藏多种多样，我们看到了
that there where a GC is stalled and you
那里GC停滞了，你
need to look into this if you think that
如果您认为这需要调查一下
you might have a memory leak and you're
您可能有内存泄漏，并且
not really sure if you see the outcome
不确定是否看到结果
most of the heap was full and it
大部分堆都装满了
shouldn't really be that's robux you can
真的不应该是鲁布克斯吗
move on to the allocation tab in JMC
转到JMC中的“分配”选项卡
which will tell you which objects has
它将告诉您哪些对象具有
been allocated of which type will also
被分配了哪种类型的
give you the stack traces where was that
给你堆栈的痕迹在哪里
those objects allocated from so you can
从中分配的那些对象
do a drill-down analysis and understand
进行深入分析并了解
why did you get a full heap and where
你为什么要堆满
could a memory come from so we looked at
可能会产生记忆，所以我们看了看
three kinds of forces and we use the
三种力量，我们使用
same method in all these cases we
在所有这些情况下，我们使用相同的方法
measured either using logging or Java
使用日志记录或Java测量
flight recorder we got a better
飞行记录仪，我们有了更好的
understanding of how it worked by yeah
了解它是如何工作的
you guys by watching this presentation
你们看了这个演讲
or you can read that Union guidelines so
或者您可以阅读该联盟准则，以便
you know what is going on and why could
你知道发生了什么，为什么可以
have cost the longer pause and then we
花了更长的停顿时间，然后我们
tuned to work around it and achieve
调整以解决它并实现
better performance so we've seen a bit
更好的性能，所以我们已经看到了一些
about the free properties throughput
关于免费属性吞吐量
latency and footprint we looked how to
延迟和占用空间，我们研究了如何
get data from an instrument a JVM we
从JVM仪器获取数据
seen how we can tune around and tune for
看到了我们如何调整和调整
lower latencies for the ball for all of
降低所有球的潜伏期
young mixed and full forces and now we
年轻的混合和全力，现在我们
want to talk a little bit about the
想谈一点
community so if you want to engage with
社区，因此，如果您想参与
us the GCC developers and also many of
我们是GCC开发人员，还有许多
the performance experts and people
表演专家和人
working will go up with collection and
工作将随着收集而增加，
orchestration tuning please sign up to
编排调整，请注册
host port GC dues on Oprah indicated
显示了Oprah上的主机端口GC费用
java.net and also thank you to all of
java.net，也感谢所有
you who are helping those who are more
那些帮助更多人的人
experienced helping out newcomers and
经验丰富的帮助新移民和
analyzing the logs we did you see
分析我们看到的日志
developers ourselves you are also
开发人员我们自己也是
reading this list but unfortunately we
阅读了这份清单，但不幸的是我们
might not always have time to answer you
可能并不总是有时间回答你
can also join the OpenJDK RC channel on
也可以加入OpenJDK RC频道
IRC that of c.net if you want to chat
如果要聊天，可以在c.net上进行IRC
with us and while you're here at yellow
和我们在一起，而当你在黄色的时候
one please stop by the Oracle developer
一个请甲骨文开发人员来
long chain was Kanye West I'm usually
长链是坎耶·韦斯特，我通常是
around in the DevOps corner you can
您可以在DevOps角落附近
learn more on open educated java.net or
了解更多关于开放教育的java.net或
work on java and if you're on twitter
在java上工作，如果你在推特上
please follow at opening decay or at
请在打开衰减处或在
worker Java and DevOps and thank you so
Java和DevOps的工作人员，非常感谢
much
许多
[Applause]
[掌声]